Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every
wall that's in our wake!
Go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up. Way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rubbed up to the sky.
Never give up. Our wishes.
They will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore.
Day by day.
There are many meetings.
Many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember.
The pain within, I'll keep
it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly,
but I won't surrender.
This freedom, I will keep in mind,
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up,
sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up, raise up
the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up, we'll get past
everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if waves are
rough, jump through the sky.
Never give up, our wishes
they will come together.
And lead us on towards our future.
Hands up.
In another five minutes, the entire
building will be filled with lethal gas.
The survivors are frantically making their
way through the lab toward building R.
At the last remaining exit, door R-66.
However...
Now the ceiling's falling in on us, too?
Look at the cracks.
The gas is seeping in.
Great, now what?
We keep going.
Get to building R.
Everyone move, but I'm scared.
I don't want to die.
Come on, this is no
time to wuss out, kids.
Now get going.
The captain's here.
I'm glad she's okay.
So you beat the bird woman, Captain?
Hold on a second.
Why are they coming from that way?
They were supposed to stay behind
to cover our escape, weren't they?
The G5 is headed straight for us.
I told you we were going in the
wrong direction, you stubborn jerk.
What?
You know what?
Forget about it and just put me down.
This is embarrassing.
There's no time for that now.
You're staying right where you are.
Zoro!
What the hell do you think
you're doing carrying
her over your shoulder
like a sack of flour?
Not this way. Turn back.
Hurry up, everybody! Run faster!
The ceiling's gonna collapse!
We need to move!
Stay or we're gonna get crushed!
Yeah, let's get out of here!
I've done all I can for now anyway!
Head straight for building our arms!
Stay with me!
We're gonna get you out of here!
That was cruel.
How am I supposed to
eat breakfast tomorrow?
You weren't supposed
to win this round, Law.
I bet you're proud of
the upset you pulled off,
but you're going to regret
what you've done here.
I promise you that.
You don't know as much about
Joker's past as you should.
And you're going to pay with
your life for that ignorance.
Upstarts like you get a touch of fame
and think they can take over the world,
but they couldn't be more wrong.
There's always someone stronger.
You're too weak to win, right, Smoker?
You runs have energy.
I'll give you that much.
But energy is enough to you.
Don't waste your breath worrying about me.
You've got your own problems to deal with.
This room's gonna explode soon.
So long, Vergo the Pirates.
there's only one man
who could have done this
it must be law why isn't
Vergo doing something
please master tell us
what's going on we've got
men buried under the
record master curse it all
this laboratory is my
paradise and it's crumbling
to pieces thanks to you the
crew i hope they're okay
our built-in floor two hey can you hear me
secret room come in do
you read me yes master
will you please tell us what just happened
open the air vents on
the first floor at once
well what are you waiting
for you heard me i
want the land of the dead
to flow into this room
but the gas is lethal i'm made of gas
it's not going to hurt me right roger
that we'll just evacuate the soldiers
from the first floor i said do it now
is there a problem do i need to define
the word now for you stop making
excuses and do as i tell you but master
there are over a hundred of our people
down there do i look like a give a
damn you fools are nothing but guinea
pigs a hundred of you could die and
nobody would even notice you were gone
let alone care you're the dregs of
society what are you doing can't you hear
me it doesn't matter how many of you
i lose you're all easily replaceable
that's gotta hurt for them seeing
caesar's true colors the others
the gas is going to get them any second i
wonder could i control the doors from here
something wrong hey i'm
asking you huh no no sir
hey wait i get it now
uh-huh the master must
be trying to fool straw
hat it's all a show Huh?
Yeah, that's right.
It's gotta be.
I bet he has a plan to
deal with the gas, too.
He wouldn't just let our people die.
There's no way!
Yeah, not a chance!
The Master's such a sensitive guy, you
would hurt him if we knew we suspected him.
Master! It's done!
I opened the vents for you!
No!
The gas is leaking in here!
We're all gonna die!
Good boy!
You should have done what
I said from the beginning!
You're here to follow orders, not think!
Now, flow into me, land of the dead!
Give me power!
Behold my full strength,
the true power of science!
Are you strong enough to
face the power of science?
This has been a very useful demonstration.
I've already had two
countries express interest
in acquiring the land of the dead from me.
Countries that are normally peaceful but
after learning a weapon like this existed
they realized they needed to protect
themselves by whatever means necessary.
My expertise will be in
high demand soon enough.
I will fill the world with weapons
I created and when that's done,
I'll take my place.
as the king of the land of the dead.
Now watch. Run!
Why, master?
He killed our brothers.
How could he? Master!
Low-life guinea pigs.
Is that really all we are?
My deadly creation works
so well, it amazes even me!
Shutting down the nervous
system almost instantaneously!
It's art as well as science!
Impossible!
How can one man possess such power?
Those poor people!
Will you look after Brownbeard?
Hey, come back here!
We were just getting started.
Ha, going to turn, tell,
and run after all—it isn't
going to do you any good though.
Not when the land of the
dead is practically filled.
Building B—there's nowhere left to run.
The entire island is a death trap now.
Hey, I know you're brokenhearted and all,
but can I take a look at
that control panel for a sec?
My friends are down there, and
I'm not gonna let them die.
You jerk—you watched the
whole time didn't you?
Let's kill him, kill me!
I wasn't the one who gassed your friends.
Yeah, he's right.
We trusted the master for years and
he betrayed us in the worst way.
What do we do now?
We didn't learn the truth
till it was too late.
There's nowhere to run.
The whole island's toxic.
You people are just as
dead as we are though.
And your captain stabbed you in the back.
Did you see him run from Caesar?
Serves you right.
He took off like a coward and
left the rest of you behind.
Wait—what was that?
Don't tell me.
I just heard you insult my captain
right in front of me. Honestly,
if he were the type of person who would
turn tail without a second thought,
things would probably be easier.
There are so many times I would
have run if it was up to me.
Now third gear but no matter what
we're up against, he never hesitates.
He never stops believing in us.
So we have no choice but
to believe in him too.
We've pledged to live up to his
expectations as long as we breathe.
Caesar may be strong
but he's the kind of person
that Luffy hates the most.
If anyone can make
Caesar pay, it's Luffy.
caesar pay it's luffy
Caesar!
I'm gonna finish you now, so I
never see you again! Come on!
Straw Hat, let's make a deal!
You can walk under me!
Let's calm down for a second intolerantly!
Come on!
Ah!
Oh!
Whoa!
he calls this an experiment well
it's a disaster after this he's
done for inform mama too sweet
ah my old joker what's next call
jack he'll handle things that's
a kind of what i was afraid of i
see an alliance this is quite a
pain well we can't allow this can we
Uppy! Uppy! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Mocha, hang in there!
Chopper, can you hear me?
Is that Usopp's voice?
Keep heading straight for
now, then go down the stairs.
That's the easiest way to get
to the R Building from there!
I need to close the shutters before
the gas gets in, so make it quick!
Oh, thanks, I'll do my best!
Topper!
What's wrong?
It's Kin'emon! Just look at him!
The gas came and then this happened!
Now he's as sad as me!
What?
Tragedy struck when we were evacuating
the children from the exam room.
We were searching for
Kinemon's lost son, Momonosuke.
We ran into a young girl who knew him.
She said something odd.
He what?
What?
Momonosuke has taken the form of a dragon?
Are you sure? Uh-huh.
It's a secret, but it's true.
Oh no.
Do you think that the dragon
we sliced up earlier could be?
Momonosuke!
I am the vilest monster that ever lived!
I won't be easily seen!
You can't go back!
That area is surely
filled with dust by now!
Ahhhh! There it is! Quick!
We must turn around at once!
A warrior spirit will guide
him through any obstacle,
be it deadly gas or a blazing fire!
Vumanosuke!
A warrior spirit or not?
That's impossible!
Well, this happened.
What was he thinking?
Luffy!
Hey, Nani!
Great, you're here already!
Oh no, what happened
to Brownie? Is he okay?
yeah he should be fine
well actually I don't know
there see I
told you don't
worry about the kids they'll
be fine my friends are on
their way to help and they
always keep their word just
worry about yourself for now
Move it!
I gotta see Nami again,
and you're holding me up!
I don't see Chopper.
That's not good.
He slowed down earlier to get first aid
to that girl, and that's all I know.
I need this. It's huge.
Yeah, that's the idea.
They use this cart to haul S .A .D.
Get it?
That means we can use it to halt
people and this whole lab is done for.
There's no time
Straw Hats
Traffy, Smoky, where'd you come from?
Smoky
Hey, look guys.
He made it.
Thank goodness.
I was so scared.
Smoky, hold on.
I'm reporting when I'm
done crying. What's that?
Shut your traps.
It's fine.
Hey, Straw Hat, where did Caesar go?
Oh, see that hole there?
I blew him straight that way.
Door kind of got busted.
What?
No, the plan was to
kidnap him. Why? He sucks.
Come on, we should just leave him behind.
That is not what we both agreed on.
If he escapes from here the
plan is ruined. I don't care.
I'm done good riddance
The point of having a plan is
to follow through with it I
should have known better than
to trust you with anything.
We got to get him back now
A short time ago, a strange sight could
be seen in the skies near Punk Hazard.
Little did the Straw Hats
know what they were in for?
Once this mission is over then I'm done.
I'll kill him. You hear me?
with my own hands.
I won't forgive you, Joker.
So cruel, it wasn't enough
to blow up my dear fiancé.
You had to burn his whole town to ash too.
He did you no wrong.
How many men must you kill?
Every time I get engaged, blow
my darling to little bits.
Eight men and eight towns.
Enough is enough.
Why won't he let me be happy? Me?
That's just how he shows his love.
He's just protective.
He thinks of you like his little
sister, that sort of thing.
Him blowing up a town or two is
just a sign of how much he cares.
Besides, this only happens because you
haven't learned how to say no to those chums.
And what made him a chump?
He said he needed me.
How could I turn my back on him?
It's love at first sight.
Will you marry me?
What?
Look here's the deal, just cuz
someone asks—you don't gotta say yes.
You don't need 50 newspaper
subscriptions; no one does,
and stop lending out all of your money—we're
wasting it on crap you don't need,
Chouchou.
How much debt do you got?
Why do you care?
It's 98 million—that's all.
This is none of your
business, if you're...
business if you're Fine.
Lend me some.
Say two mil.
What?
He needs me.
Um, can I pay you later?
Mm-hmm.
When we're done, I needed to go gambling.
Okay, then.
Once we finish our mission, I'll
take out a new loan for you.
Joker needed me to carry this out.
After that, it's over.
Bastard's as good as dead.
That's it!
Honk Hazard, straight ahead!
I can't see anything.
Caesar's gas is covering the whole island.
If I shoot it, will that help any?
No way! Hop off!
I've got this, no problem.
I'll be quick!
It's typhoon time!
Let's go!
Storm God! Matagamuro!
They'll be here soon.
Caesar, Monet, and Vergo, too.
I sure can't wait to spend
all your money at the casino!
Did one of the tanks just explode?
No, something went flying into the ship!
Not something, someone.
Joker, Mrs.
Buffalo, I got you!
That's a bad news.
What's up?
Well, you see, we made it.
But it looks like something
went down before we got here.
We just saw Master Caesar,
but he was all busted up.
He went flying out of the
lab and into the tanker.
Like someone kicked his ass hard.
Is that so?
I don't care what state he's in.
Grab Caesar immediately.
Get out of there and
bring him to dress Rosa.
But Monet and Vanko!
Just do what he says.
There must be some reason.
Okay! So long!
Bunch of damn rookies.
Blow up the lab.
What the hell do I care?
It'll take more than that to beat me.
All that matters is Caesar.
As long as I have him, I can
make all the S .A .D. I need.
Wait, there's someone down on the
deck, but that can't be right.
No way, not with all that gas.
You sure it's not just some
dead body or something?
It's a robot!
Man, that's what messed up looking bird.